arri.com 2017-11-20

# ARRI Group: Privacy Declaration

Privacy Declaration

ARRI AG (hereafter known as ARRI) is obliged to protect your personal data. By using the website and the online content of ARRI, you agree in advance to this Privacy Declaration.  
You personal data is collected, processed and used exclusively within the scope of the provisions of the privacy protection statutes (data protection statues) of the Federal Republic of Germany. Information concerning the nature, extent and purpose of the collection, processing and use of personal data is provided below. You can view this information at any time on our website.

1\. Which data is collected, processed and used by ARRI  
Generally speaking, you are not required to state who you are or provide any personal data in order to visit the website of ARRI or view the website content. To enable ARRI to sell products to you and/or to provide you with information on certain services, including customer service and/or information related to products or services, and/or to enable you to make full use of the website content, it is necessary to collect suitable personal data on the relevant pages of the website or the online content and in the relevant data entries. This includes in particular, but not exclusively, your personal information or company details, such as your name, company name, address, age, telephone and fax numbers, e-mail addresses and other contact data; information on products, such as serial number, product site, configuration and other product-related data and/or information regarding product purchases, as well as references to your identification particulars and details, including use profiles, information on the start and end of use of the online content, and scope of use. Furthermore, for technical reasons data may be collected automatically when our website is accessed, such as the date and time of access, the URL of the referring website, the files viewed, the volume of data sent, the browser type and version, the operating system, and your IP address. (The data mentioned above is hereafter collectively referred to as personal data.)

2\. Use and disclosure of your personal data  
ARRI may collect, process and use your personal data to:

  * fulfil its obligations under the provisions of the purchase contract as well as other contractual agreements between you and ARRI;
  * provide customer service, including services in connection with the business operations of ARRI, such as warranties, guarantees and customer service;
  * make upgrades, updates and bug fixes for your products available to you;
  * obtain your opinion on ARRI products and services and conduct product surveys;
  * simplify and process your search transactions and your requests for data and for the products and services of ARRI;
  * provide you with the latest information on ARRI products and services, including suggestions and special offers that you may be interested in;
  * improve ARRI’s products and services for you;
  * conduct competitions, contests and other promotional offers and marketing activities;
  * ensure that you are only able to access this website by means of the interface provided by ARRI for this purpose.

ARRI stores your personal data solely in order to fulfil the purpose for which it was originally collected or in order to comply with the provisions of applicable laws and regulations.

ARRI may share personal data with other ARRI affiliated companies in Europe and worldwide, make personal data available to them or convey personal data to them, subject to the condition that ARRI must nevertheless strictly comply with applicable privacy protection legislation. ARRI affiliated companies use your personal data only for the purposes mentioned above, and they are subject to strict principles and rules regarding the use and protection of personal data. (ARRI affiliated companies comprise all companies, firms, and partnerships for which the majority of their shares or equity is owned directly or indirectly by ARRI or is controlled by ARRI.)

External companies receive personal data only to the extent necessary to provide the service concerned. We do not allow external companies to use your personal data for any other purpose.

It may be necessary for us to access your personal data or disclose your personal data in order to comply with the provisions of applicable laws or court proceedings or to assert our rights or defend ourselves against legal claims. We will disclose personal data and all other available information if necessary in order to investigate unlawful activities, suspected fraud, potential threats to the corporeal integrity of persons or violations of the conditions of use specified by ARRI, or to take preventive measures or countermeasures in this regard. Data may additionally be conveyed for other reasons to the extent required or permitted by law.  
  
3\. How ARRI collects personal data  
ARRI collects data about you in various ways. For example, we request your contact data when you correspond with ARRI, call ARRI to make a purchase or request customer service, register your purchased products with our customer service department, or register in order to view our online content, support, or material available for downloading.

The most common examples of how ARRI collects your personal data are:

  * When you register an ARRI product or service, we collect your name, address, and other contact data, as well as the product name or model name, product site, etc.
  * When you request help from our customer service department, we record your name, contact data, the purchased product, product site, technical problem concerned, advice provided, etc.
  * When you purchase a product from us or have a purchasing question, we record your name, contact data, the products you have purchased or wish to purchase, and your questions.
  * When you use our website and our online content, make a purchase online or use the download areas, if necessary we create an account for you with your contact data, product data, payment preferences and delivery preferences. In some cases it is necessary to make a credit check if you wish to purchase a product or service.

Data collected online may also be combined with data you have made available to ARRI at other times, such as during the purchasing process, product registrations, calls to ARRI, or at public events such as exhibitions and fairs. The personal data received by ARRI in such cases is compared with existing data in databases and stored in order to simplify our customer data management system.

The personal data that we collect may be stored in various databases. ARRI strives to respect the various preferences you have expressed at various times in order to process your data appropriately. If you ever receive incorrect data for whatever reason, please contact ARRI in order to correct the situation.  
  
4\. Security of collected personal data  
ARRI takes due care to protect your personal data against loss and misuse. ARRI strives to the best of its ability to take all suitable technical and organisational measures and precautionary measures in order to protect personal data against unauthorised access, improper use, changes, loss or destruction. These measures comprise: 

  * Restricting access to personal data. Only employees who need to know the data in order to offer you products and services are allowed access.
  * Using physical, electronic and process-based security mechanisms conforming to regulations in order to protect your personal data.
  * Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) encryption for the collection and transmission of sensitive data, such as credit card details.

5\. Cookies  
We use cookies to expand the functional scope of our web content and make it easier for you to use the site. These cookies can be used to store data on your computer when you visit our website and view our online content. It is possible to prevent the storage of cookies on your computer by configuring the settings of your browser accordingly, although this may restrict the functional scope of our website content.

6\. Google Analytics  
This website uses Google Analytics, a web analytics service provided by Google Inc. ("Google"). Google Analytics uses "cookies," which are text files placed on your computer that enable an analysis of your use of the website. The information generated by the cookie about your use of this website is generally transmitted to and stored on a Google server in the United States. In case of activation of IP anonymization on this website, Google will, however, truncate your IP address beforehand within Member States of the European Union or other parties to the Agreement on the European Economic Area. Only in exceptional cases will the full IP address be transmitted to a Google server in the United States and truncated there. On behalf of the operator of this website, Google will use this information for the purpose of evaluating your use of the website, compiling reports on website activity and providing the website operator with other services relating to website and Internet use. The IP address transmitted by your browser within the scope of Google Analytics will not be associated with any other data held by Google.

You may refuse the use of cookies by selecting the appropriate settings in your browser; however, please note that if you do so, you may not be able to use the full functionality of this website. Furthermore, you can prevent Google’s collection and use of data generated by the cookie and related to your use of the website (including your IP address) by downloading and installing the browser plug-in available at (<http://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout?hl=en>).

For further information on terms of use and data protection/privacy, please see [www.google.com/analytics/terms/us.html or www.google.com/analytics/learn/index.html](http://www.google.com/analytics/terms/us.html). Please note that on this website, Google Analytics has been supplemented by the code "gat._anonymizeIp();" in order to ensure anonymized collection of IP addresses ("IP masking").

7\. Google AdWords (Remarketing / Conversion Tracking)  
Our website uses Google AdWords. Google AdWords is an online advertising program from Google Inc., 1600 Amphitheater Parkway, Mountain View, CA 94043, USA ("Google").

We use the remarketing feature within the Google AdWords service. With the remarketing feature, we can present users of our website on other websites within the Google Display Network (on Google itself, so-called "Google Ads", or other sites) advertising based on their interests. Therefore, the interaction of the users on our website is analyzed, e.g. in which offers the user was interested in, in order to be able to display the targeted advertisements to the users even after visiting our website on other sites. Google stores a cookie in the browsers of users who visit specific Google services or Google Display Network sites. This cookie is used to record visits by these users. This browser is used to uniquely identify a web browser on a specific computer and not to identify a person, and personal data will not be stored. You may opt out of Google's use of cookies by following the link below and downloading and installing the plug-in provided: <https://www.google.com/settings/ads/plugin>. For more information about Google's remarketing and Google's privacy policy, visit <http://www.google.com/privacy/ads/>.

We also use conversion tracking as part of the Google AdWords service. When you click on a Google-served ad, a conversion tracking cookie is placed on your computer device. These cookies lose their validity after 30 days, contain no personal data and thus do not serve for personal identification. The information that is collected using the conversion cookie is used to create conversion statistics for AdWords customers who have opted for conversion tracking.

You can prevent cookies from being saved by setting your browser software accordingly; however, we would point out that in this case you may not be able to fully utilize all the functions of this website. In addition, you can disable interest-based ads on Google, as well as interest-based Google ads on the web (within the Google Display Network) in your browser by clicking the "Off" button at [www.google.com/settings/ads](http://www.google.com/settings/ads) or deactivate it at <http://www.aboutads.info/choices/>. For more information about your Google's setting options and privacy, visit <https://www.google.com/intl/en/policies/privacy/?fg=1>.

8\. Social networks  
This website uses plugins/functions from the Facebook and Twitter social networks. These are disabled by default for data protection reasons and must be activated explicitly by you to be used. Before activation, please note the following information on individual service providers:

Facebook  
This website uses social plugins from the facebook.com social network provided by Facebook Inc., 1601 South California Avenue, Palo Alto, CA 94304, USA. You can recognize the plugins by the Facebook logo and/or “Like” button. Provided you access a page with such a plugin when visiting this website, your Internet browser will establish a direct connection to the servers of Facebook Inc. The content of the plugin is transferred to your Internet browser and integrated by it into the page shown. At the same time, the information that you visited this website is transferred to Facebook Inc. If you are logged into your personal Facebook user account when accessing the relevant page, Facebook Inc. will assign the website visit to your user account.

When you use the plugin, e.g. by clicking on the “Like” button, this information is directly transferred to Facebook Inc. and stored there. In this way, Facebook can assign the information when you visit our pages to your user account. If you would like to prevent such data from being transferred, you must log out of your Facebook user account before visiting our Internet website.

Please note that we, as a provider of the pages, are not informed of the content of the transferred data and its use by Facebook. The active use of the plugin is subject to the data protection conditions and the terms of use of Facebook Inc. For more information on the collection, storage and use of your data by Facebook Inc., please see the Facebook data protection policies (<https://www.facebook.com/policy.php>) and the privacy policy (<https://www.facebook.com/privacy/explanation>.)

Facebook Pixel  
With your consent, we use the "Facebook Pixel" of Facebook Inc., 1601 S. California Ave, Palo Alto, CA 94304, USA ( "Facebook") within our website. We can use it to track the actions of users who have seen or clicked on a Facebook ad. This allows us to track the effectiveness of Facebook advertising for statistical and market research purposes and can help optimize future advertising measures. The data collected in this way is anonymous for us, therefore offer no conclusions regarding the identity of the users. However, this data will be stored and processed by Facebook, which will be communicated to you according to our knowledge. Facebook can connect this data with its Facebook account and also use its own advertising, according to Facebook's data usage policy <https://www.facebook.com/about/privacy/> . You can enable Facebook as well as its partners to turn advertising ads on and off Facebook. For this purpose, a cookie can also be stored on your computer.

This consent may be declared only by users older than 13 years of age. If you are younger, please ask your educated persons for advice.

To change your settings and remove Facebook's visitor action pixel, please use this link:  <https://www.facebook.com/ads/website_custom_audiences/>. The data disclosed to Facebook will be transmitted outside of Europe to other jurisdictions, including the United States.

Twitter  
With Twitter and Retweet functions, we use plugins from twitter.com provided by Twitter Inc., 795 Folsom St., Suite 600, San Francisco, CA 94107, USA.

If you use the Retweet functions, the websites you visit are disclosed to third parties and are connected to your Twitter account. In the process, data is also transferred to Twitter.

Please note that we, as a provider of the pages, are not informed of the content of the transferred data and its use by Twitter. For information on the way your data is handled by Twitter Inc. as well as on your rights and setting options for the protection of your personal data, please refer to the data protection advice from Twitter (<http://twitter.com/privacy>). You can change your data protection settings at Twitter under account settings.

9\. Crazy Egg  
We use the Crazy Egg analysis services provided by Crazy Egg, Inc., 16220 E. Ridgeview Lane, La Mirada, CA 90638, USA. uses first-party cookies to detect if visitors to our website are returning visitors or first-time visitors. The default expiration date of the cookies is five years. This can be changed by setting a global JavaScript variable, as described here [help.crazyegg.com/articles/43-new-vs-returning-visitors](http://help.crazyegg.com/articles/43-new-vs-returning-visitors).

Crazy Egg Analysis service collects standard internet log information to track visitor behavior information. The following information will be collected: Browser Information, Operating System Information, Mobile Device Information (e.g., device identifier, mobile operating system, etc.), IP Address, Page Accessed, Geographic Location, Time of Visit, Referring Site, Application, or Service. The information generated by cookies about use of this website (including the IP addresses of visitors) is transmitted to Crazy Egg. This information is used by us to compile statistical reports on the website’s activities and enhance the user online experience.

For more information about Crazy Egg’s Privacy Policy, please visit [www.crazyegg.com/privacy](http://www.crazyegg.com/privacy).  Those wishing to opt-out of Crazy Egg Analytics data collection should use [www.crazyegg.com/opt-out](http://www.crazyegg.com/opt-out). Note that the opt-out is only valid on the Internet browser and computer that the visitor used to opt-out, so the opt-out link will need to be revisited in order to reset opt-out preferences if a new Internet browser or computer are used to access our website.  

Crazy Egg may share visitor information it collects with third-party companies and individuals that help facilitate technical aspects of the service, and may disclose visitor information in accordance with its Privacy Policy.

The data disclosed to Crazy Egg will be transmitted outside of Europe to other jurisdictions, including the United States.

10\. Newsletter  
We offer you the opportunity to subscribe to our newsletter. For the dispatch of our newsletter, we use Newsletter2Go, an offer of Newsletter2Go GmbH, Marie-Elisabeth-Lüders-Str. 1, D-10625 Berlin. Newsletter2Go has its principal place of business in Germany and data protection legislation of Germany applies. 

Newsletter2Go offers extensive analytics tools for analyzing how the newsletters are opened and used. In addition, Newsletter2Go uses the web analytics tool Google Analytics incorporating it into newsletters.

You can revoke your consent to storage of data, the e-mail address as well as its use for the dispatch of the newsletter, at any time. 

The revocation can be made via a link in the newsletters themselves or by notifying our contact options as specified under point 10.

11\. Right to receive information, correct, block and delete personal data  
On request and with no need to state a reason, you may at any time receive information concerning your data stored by us. You may at any time block, correct or delete your data collected by us. You may at any time revoke the declaration of consent given to us for the collection, processing and use of personal data, with no need to state a reason. To do so, please communicate with ARRI at the address stated under point 9 by fax, telephone or letter.

On request, you will receive a declaration regarding the processing of your personal data, as well as confirmation that all parties concerned have been informed of your information request with regard to modification, blocking or deletion. ARRI will do everything within its power to fulfil these requests.

If you wish to be deleted from an e-mail distribution list (such as for a newsletter), please use the Unsubscribe link and/or follow the instructions that are (normally) included in the footer of the e-mail message, or contact ARRI at the address mentioned under point 9 by fax, telephone or post.

12\. Links to other sites  
Some ARRI websites contain links to other websites that are not administered by ARRI. Your personal data is not shared with these websites. Although ARRI strives to offer only links to sites that comply with the high standards of ARRI with regard to personal privacy, ARRI does not bear any responsibility for the content, security or privacy practices of other sites and expressly disavows any liability in connection with the use of other sites and the content found on other sites.

13\. Child protection (children aged 14 years or less)  
ARRI does not knowingly acquire or collect personal data from children or about children (aged 14 years or less) without the permission of their parents or guardians, and ARRI does not knowingly market any products or services to children If ARRI becomes aware that a person whose personal data has been submitted via an ARRI website is a child, ARRI will do everything in its power to delete this personal data as quickly as possible. ARRI will do everything in its power to ensure that this personal data is not used for any other purpose or disclosed to other parties.

14\. Contact  
If you need additional assistance or wish to submit a comment, request or declaration, please contact us at the following address or by means of one of the contact options stated below:

Address:  
ARRI AG  
Türkenstrasse 89  
80799 Munich  
Germany

Contact data:  
Tel.: +49 (0)89 3809 0  
Fax: +49 (0)89 3809 1244  
E-mail: [webmaster@arri.de](mailto:webmaster@arri.de)

Last updated: 2017
